goingon.com 2007-09-23

# Privacy Policy | GoingOn Home

PRIVACY POLICY 

Your privacy is important, so GoingOn Networks, Inc. has created the following Privacy Policy to let you know what information we collect when you visit our Site, why we collect it and how it is used. This Privacy Policy explains the data collection and use practices of goingon.com, a weblog publishing and community management platform for corporations, media companies, nonprofits, and other organizations; it does not apply to other online or offline GoingOn sites, products or services. The terms “you,” “your,” and “yours” refer to the customer/purchaser utilizing our Site. The terms “GoingOn,” “we,” “us,” and “our” refer to GoingOn Networks, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates. This Privacy Policy is governed by our  [Terms and Conditions ](http://www.goingon.com/company/terms/condition) . By using this web site, you consent to the data practices prescribed in this statement. We may periodically make changes to this Privacy Policy that we will include on this page. It is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy frequently and remain informed about any changes to it, so we encourage you to visit this page often. 

What Information Is Collected? 

“Personally Identifiable Information”  means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, home or other physical address, an email address, phone number or other contact information, whether at work or at home.  GoingOn  collects the following Personally Identifiable Information from you when you use our Site:  first and last name, email address. Any additional information is not required but provided by the user at his/her discretion. GoingOn  also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information and the page you request. You can change your GoingOn account settings, including your profile information, at any time in the Edit Profile section. You can edit, save drafts and remove your posts at any time, as described in the Help section. If you delete your weblog, we will remove all posts from public view. Because of the way we maintain this service, residual copies of your profile information and other information associated with your account may remain on back-up media. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. 

Is The Information Shared or Disclosed? 

GoingOn does not rent, sell or share personal information it collects about you to or with third parties. Information collected from you is only used to complete and support your purchases from and use of the GoingOn Site and to comply with any requirements of law. GoingOn may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on GoingOn or this web site; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of GoingOn; or (3) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of GoingOn, its web sites or the public. If GoingOn should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another GoingOn, we may sell the information you provide to us on this Site to a third party or share your Personally Identifiable Information with any company with whom we merge. 

Choice. 

“Please be aware that this Privacy Policy and the choices you make on this web site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to  GoingOn  in the context of other, separately operated,  GoingOn  products or services.” 

Access. 

To update any of your personal information or to change any of your marketing preferences, you may either contact us at  [](mailto:%66%65%65%64%62%61%63%6B%40%67%6F%69%6E%67%6F%6E%2E%63%6F%6D) or in certain cases you may update your personal information through the Site by logging in and accessing your profile in the "My Account" area. 

The Security of Your Information. 

GoingOn  protects the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you input. 

International Transfers. 

Personal Information collected on this web site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which  GoingOn  or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this web site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

GoingOn  abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. 

Children. 

This Site is not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 13.  GoingOn  does not sell products for purchase by children.  GoingOn  sells children’s products for purchase by adults. Any person who provides their information to  GoingOn  through the Account Login page for new customers or any other part of the  GoingOn  Site represents to  GoingOn  that they are 13 years of age or older. 

Cookies. 

Cookies are small text files stored by your browser in your computer when you visit our Site. We use cookies to improve our Site and make it easier to use. Cookies permit us to recognize users and avoid repetitive requests for the same information. We mostly use “session cookies” that are automatically deleted after each visit. Cookies from our Site can not be read by other Sites. Most browsers will accept cookies until you change your browser settings to refuse them. 

Your Consent To This Privacy Policy. 

By using this Site, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. Our  [Terms and Conditions ](http://www.goingon.com/company/terms/condition) take precedence over any conflicting Privacy Policy provision. We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new version of this Privacy Policy on this Site which it is your responsibility to review. 

Contacting GoingOn. 

If you believe that  GoingOn  has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at  [](mailto:%66%65%65%64%62%61%63%6B%40%67%6F%69%6E%67%6F%6E%2E%63%6F%6D) or by postal mail at  PO Box 620100 Woodside, CA 94062  and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to remedy the problem.
